

DANG VAN SANG

FRESHER FRONT-END DEVELOPER

CONTACT INFO

22/03/1993

sangdang2203@gmail.com 43/17 Street 8, Linh Trung

Ward, Thu Duc City, Ho Chi Minh City.

0909 751 772

https://www.linkedin.com/in/da ng-van-sang/

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JS, ANGULAR JS

SQL & DATABASE

GREAT COMMUNICATION SKILLS

SITUATION HANDLING SKILLS

CUSTOMER PERSUASION SKILLS

TEAMWORK SKILLS

ENGLISH

INTERESTS

Get the experiences.

Listen to instrumental music.

Sea travel

Gastronomy

Introduction

Besides the desire to study and work in a professional environment, sociable colleagues; I want to become a good Developer, want to contribute to the development - upgrade - maintain the stability of the product, make a certain contribution to the development of company.

Projects

◆ EPROJECT SEM 01: CHIC LIGHTING & DESIGN

14/01/2023 - 28/02/2023

- Technologies used: HTML5, CSS, JSON, Angular JS, JavaScript.
- eProject requirements: Design front-end for website Chic Lighting
 & Design specializing in LED Lights, Lighting, Chandeliers and
 Pendant Lights.
- **Github:** https://github.com/Sangdang2203/eProject_Sem01
- eProject published at: https://sangdang2203.github.io/eProject_Sem01/#!/home

Work Experiences

◆ HUTTONS VN COMPANY LIMITED

02/2022 - Present

Agency Manager

- Oriented and supported the team (4 people) to achieve 11 transactions with a total value of more than 60 billions .
- ◆ HOANG GIA REAL ESTATE SERVICE 04/2017 05/2021 CO..LTD

Sale Executive, Sale Team Leader

- Best seller period 2018 2019.
- Oriented and supported the team (4 persons) to reach 10 transactions with a total value of about 60 billions.
- Excellent project management for the period 2019-2020: Orienting and supporting Business Department (12 persons) to achieve good results with a total value of about 160 billions.

REFERENCE PERSON

Mr. Dao Nguyen Vinh

Co-Founder at HOANG GIA REAL ESTATE SERVICE CO.,LTD

Q 0903 686162

Mr. Nguyen Tuan Anh

Co-Founder at HOANG GIA REAL ESTATE SERVICE CO.,LTD

Q 0933 848833

◆ RTBD CO., LTD 12/2015 - 11/2016

Sale Executive

◆ **PHAT PHAT ESTATE CO.,LTD** 09/2014 - 10/2015

Sale Executive

Educations

◆ HO CHI MINH CITY UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY - HUTECH.

09/2011 - 10/2014

Major: Business Administration

Graduated with a good Bachelor's degree.

◆ FPT POLYTECHNIC COLLEGE OF PRACTICE.

10/2022 - Present

Major: Information Technology (Aptech)